<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Morey Wood</title>
    <description>Looking for Opportunities to Design, Implement, and Evaluate User Interfaces to Improve Overall Usability and Create Positive User Experiences.</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2016 00:27:28 -0600</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2016 00:27:28 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.3.1</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Graduate Research Assistant at Center for Advanced Vehicular Systems</title>
        <description>
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2016 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/work/2016/12/01/gradassistant.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/work/2016/12/01/gradassistant.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>work</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Auto Manufacturer Project II</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Worked with the manufacturer and their suppliers to design software solution to improve workflow. Created interactive mockups using the InVision prototyping tool to get feedback on early designs. Led the team in development of the application after the design was approved.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2016 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/project/2016/12/01/automanufacturerII.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/project/2016/12/01/automanufacturerII.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>project</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Auto Manufacturer Project I</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Developed an application to simplify the process of creating reports on incidents from the factory floor. Assumed responsibility for development of the iPad version the app after a previous team member departed the project. Developed the app using Swift and Realm Mobile Database. Preserved the core of the original interface design while accommodating new requirements.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2016 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/project/2016/12/01/automanufacturerI.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/project/2016/12/01/automanufacturerI.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>project</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Employee Scheduling App</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Designed and implemented a multi-platform application to allow temporary employees to schedule working hours themselves rather than needing to contact someone at the company. Used InVision to provide interactive prototypes during development to show stakeholders how the final app would function. Was responsible for the HTML/CSS/Sass to create the interface for the app, as well as a large portion of the app’s functionality through JavaScript. The app has since been rolled out to employees.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2015 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/project/2015/05/01/SchedulingApp.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/project/2015/05/01/SchedulingApp.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>project</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Undergraduate Research Assistant at Center for Advanced Vehicular Systems</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;This project involved the design, implementation, and evaluation of an interface for multi-user decision making for product acquisitions.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2015 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/work/2015/05/01/undergradassistant.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/work/2015/05/01/undergradassistant.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>work</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Intern Programmer Analyst at FedEx Services</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Developed a mobile application to aid in servicing remote servers by using Microsoft Azure to store and interpret information. Built a cross-platform mobile app for Android, iOS, and Windows Phone was built using an Agile development methodology. Received Fan Favorite, Customer Focus, and Director’s Choice awards.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2014 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/work/2014/05/07/fedex.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/work/2014/05/07/fedex.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>work</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Intern at United States Marine Inc.</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Provided technical support, developed tools to automate time consuming procedure and conducted hardware and software surveys to allow for better management of hardware and software licenses.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/work/2013/05/07/usmi.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/work/2013/05/07/usmi.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>work</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Intern at NVision Solutions</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Explored and reported on three open source alternatives to currently in-use products. Created Geographic Information System prototypes to allow users to log incident locations and descriptions on a map and subsequently store that information in a database for later use.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 07 May 2012 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/work/2012/05/07/nvision.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/work/2012/05/07/nvision.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>work</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
